Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
You just got in trouble for fighting.
Now you want to get in trouble for gambling too?
If you wanted to yell at me, you should’ve done that when—
Are you hurt?
I’m not joking, P’Niran.
I’m really worried about you.
You’re my whole world.
I’ll protect this world.
So what did the teacher say?
He asked me to pick up 100 pieces of trash.
Right now?
Well… what star am I like?
The North Star.
I like the North Star more than anything in the world.
Look at him.
He’s probably floating off into space.
Do you miss Nong Cheewa, P’Niran?
Nong, my ass.
Why am I even on
the same color team as you?
I would’ve signed up for judo to throw you.
Asshole,
are you going to throw me every day?
Enough already.
If not “Nong”,
then what should we call him, P’Niran?
You guys are talking nonsense.
By the way,
what color team are
Cheewa, Jomyut, and Newton on?
The Blue team.
How do you know?
Well…
Don’t you have to leave early today?
We’ve only ever gone home together.
I want to go to school with you for a change.
You can’t walk with me, kid.
Our color teams are direct rivals.
Hey, I’m just kidding.
Did you know?
You're an early Gemini.
I'm a late Gemini.
We're not that far apart in age.
You don’t have to call me “Nong” anymore.
If you don’t want me to call you “Nong,”
then what should I call you?
How about…
“Little one”?
Hmm?
Little one.
P’Cheewin told me
he calls his partner “little one.”
Do you really want to call me that, P’Niran?
I don’t know. Just call me whatever you want.
How about you call me Mr.?
Young Master Niran, did you know?
Oh, come on.
Why can’t you tell
when I’m joking or being serious?
Let’s go.
I don’t want your student council
or your president’s gang scolding me.
So observant.
Well, well, well!
Shut up, guys.
I think he’s really down bad.
Hey, are we competing in any sports?
Sports again?
We did that last year.
You really want to do it again this year?
Can I use the seniors’ quota to skip it?
Yeah.
I don’t think I’m competing this year.
I’m lazy.
What about you, Niran?
Are you doing any sports?
Even if you don’t sign up,
your team will come begging you to.
Niran.
So lucky
we’re on the same color team again.
Do you want to play any sports this year?
See? I was spot on.
Call me Master Hem.
Hello, Master.
Do I really have to this year?
I’m in Grade 12 already. Can I skip it?
Let the juniors play.
The juniors are begging for you.
They all want their P’Niran to compete.
Mm.
Please. Just compete in something.
Alright then.
Let me sign you up.
Niran.
Mr. Niran, are you looking for me?
Mr.? Don’t call me that.
It sounds so distant.
Alright.
You don’t like us being distant.
My heart is full now.
What’s he talking about?
Are you sleepy?
Well, I don’t have classes.
And the others are busy with their activities.
So yeah, a little.
Seniors have it the easiest, huh?
How?
I don’t have it easy at all.
P’Niran, did you know
why dinosaurs became extinct?
Because an asteroid hit Earth?
Wrong.
Because on a meteor shower night,
a dinosaur made a wish on that shooting star
that it wanted 10,000 more wishes.
After that,
10,000 more meteors
came crashing down on Earth.
Hmm…
Funny, right?
I know you like cracking jokes.
So I did the math.
Out of the 48 jokes I came up with,
I figured you’d like this one the most.
That’s great.
Do you want to hear some more?
I wrote them all down.
No, I’m good.
And please don’t say that to anyone else.
Or they might copy your line.
What are you doing here?
My friends asked me to buy stuff for them.
Wanna help me?
Of course.
Where are Jomyut and Newton?
I haven’t seen them.
They’re at the club, working on
an upgraded version of the alien detector.
Again?
Haven’t they learned?
The janitor’s going to
chase them down the building again.
Are you sure you don’t want me
to help you carry those?
They’re light as a feather.
But you asked for my help.
I didn’t ask you to help carry them.
I just wanted you to keep me company.
Can’t you do that?
Cheewa, watch out!
Cheewa!
I’m so sorry again, Cheewa.
It’s normal.
When an object like a ball
weighing approximately 450 grams
comes hurtling at 30 kilometers per hour
or more,
the impact can cause a nosebleed
and blurred vision.
Cheewa.
Your glasses are broken.
You’re bleeding too.
Let’s go to the nurse’s office now.
Are you okay? Are you still dizzy?
It’s really bad.
The snacks! I forgot the snacks!
Without your glasses,
you look pretty handsome.
A bit less handsome than me.
How nearsighted are you?
Almost -10.
That must make your life really difficult.
Not that difficult.
Drink some water.
Hey, hey, hey!
I think it does make it difficult.
Yeah.
My mom is only -4,
and she’s already complaining that
she can’t find the remote in her hand.
What are you going to do?
Do you have a spare pair?
Do we need to call P’Cheewin to bring them?
I don’t have a spare pair.
Well then.
Please take care of him, P’Niran.
Just stick to P’Niran like toffee, kid.
You better have your glasses ready tomorrow.
P’Niran has a judo match.
Every year on Sports Day,
the school president is pretty busy
taking care of all the color teams,
but I’ll make sure to be there for you, P’Niran.
Ooooh!
You guys are crazy.
Get it together.
Alright, drink some water.
I’ve been holding it for a while.
What’s toffee?
No idea.
It’s a candy.
You know, the kind that comes on a stick.
Why does it stick together?
I heard it’s sticky.
RED TEAM
Hey, kid.
Do you want to go back to your Blue team?
Huh?
Open your mouth.
Ouch!
I’m sorry.
You’re supposed to eat the snack,
not my fingers.
Is the snack sweet, buddy?
You’re snacking with him.
How could you be lonely?
Don’t bite my fingers.
To the left.
My left.
Stay still. I’ll put it in.
Good job.
I’ll give you a reward.
Turn around three times.
Yeah.
You’re so easy to take care of.
GO, RED TEAM!
Ah!
Who were you feeding just now?
P’Niran, of course.
Really?
Now, feed yourself.
One more time.
Feed yourself.
Make it funny.
This isn’t funny. No one’s behind you.
Feed yourself.
You really can’t see?
It’s here.
Yeah.
Shake them off too.
Watch your head.
Now that I get a good look at you,
you’re pretty handsome.
Even though I can’t see very clearly,
I can hear you.
What’s wrong?
I get shy too, you know?
Mm.
Can we go now?
Can you see?
Not really.
Hold onto my shirt then.
Hold onto my arm.
Can you walk okay?
Can I ride on your back?
Don’t be ridiculous.
I’m sorry.
I can’t really see.
That’s pretty bad.
Here.
No. Whoa, it’s really bad.
I got this from the science room.
I thought you might find it useful.
Is that okay?
Does it help?
You have such doe eyes.
I feel so much better
now that I can see you up close.
Yeah, just do whatever you want.
You actually look like an alien.
Are you an alien?
Huh?
You looked through it and drank the water?
There!
Hey.
What a mess.
Hold my hand
so you don’t trip getting on the bus.
Hold my shoulders.
M.W.B.
I don’t think we’re getting any seats.
We can stand.
Are you sure?
Hold my hand
so you don’t trip getting on the bus.
Are you okay?
It’s harder than I thought.
Here, stand like this.
Hold my shoulders.
Is this okay?
Yes.
P’Niran, did you know that
from where we stand,
if the driver brakes,
gravity could make me hug you from behind?
What is it now?
Stop talking.
Hold on properly.
I said, hold on properly.
Okay.
Hold on properly!
What kind of driving is that?
Gosh!
We’ve arrived.
Is this it?
By the way,
I’ve never walked you home before,
even though we live so close.
Nice house.
Not really.
Do you need me to walk you inside?
Or can you manage?
Do you want to come inside?
No, it’s fine.
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
P’Niran.
Good luck tomorrow.
I’m competing against the Blue team.
Are you sure you want to
cheer for your opponent?
Damn.
I’m excited.
I haven’t seen this vibe in so long.
Thipok, why aren’t you on the drums?
Hype your friends up.
Cheering is more fun.
Let the juniors take care of that.
Who do you think Cheewa is rooting for?
One of them is from his team.
The other is his opponent,
but the owner of his heart.
If Niran hears you say that,
he’s going to throw you.
Wait, but Cheewa said
he’d come to cheer him on, didn’t he?
I haven’t seen him.
Honestly, I don’t think
the president’s crew would have the time.
There he is!
Woo!
Go, Niran!
It doesn’t matter how much cheer you get.
What matters is if the person you like
shows up to cheer for you.
You’re freaking distracting him.
Stop it, Hem.
Athletes from both teams,
please exchange bows!
May I also ask both cheering squads
to quiet down?
Our athletes need to focus.
Begin!
I’m competing against the Blue team.
Are you sure you want to
cheer for your opponent?
Sports Day won't affect my grades.
Of course I'm going to
cheer for my crush’s team.
Fine. Just make sure
you get there in time to cheer.
It’s okay.
You can still try for third place.
What’s wrong?
You looked completely distracted
during the match.
You don't usually lose your edge this easily.
He was really distracted
because someone from the Blue team
came to sit on our side.
You’re running your mouth again, P’Hem.
Don’t blame my friend.
Oh, hey, Jom, my dear bro.
I haven’t really seen you around lately.
I, Newton, and the other members
are working on a top-secret alien exploration mission.
We’re not sitting around doing nothing
like you guys.
Yeah, it’s really top secret.
No one knows about it.
Yeah.
Come on.
Ouch!
Here’s some water.
Thanks.
Would you like anything else to eat?
All of us are here
and you only bought one bottle?
Let’s go grab some cold water.
I’m thirsty too.
Come on.
We don’t have anyone to buy it for us.
There’s a whole group of us
and he only got one bottle.
What are you waiting for? Let’s go.
Are you feeling better?
I just lost a Sports Day match.
You don’t have to comfort me.
I thought you said Sports Day
doesn’t have anything to do with grades.
It’s okay.
Free hugs.
You're the best in my eyes, P’Niran.
No matter how many times you lose,
you'll always win my heart.
Thanks.
I’m touched.
This is it.
I’m definitely winning you over.
Hmm…
Are you going to let me hug you all night?
I’m free tonight.
Hmm…
This kid.
You little puppy.
Damn. As soon as they heard
the Astronomy Club has AC on,
they all came freeloading.
You’re welcome to visit often, P’Niran.
Yeah, I’m sensitive to AC, though.
But I guess I could sneak in for a nap.
I smelled it earlier when we hugged.
Are you wearing perfume again?
I just wanted to impress you.
Do you like it?
Why are you smiling?
Stop smiling.
Why not?
Don’t smile.
Sorry.
I can’t stop smiling.
Let me smile with my back turned.
Watch out!
Hi.
Are you seriously not going to
get a single thing right?
You don’t even care about studying.
Please calm down.
What the hell is it this time?
Did you really think you’d scared me off
after messing with me last time?
This time, you dressed as a ghost
to punch me.
Asshole, what’s your problem with me?
Why?
- What do you want?
- What are you gonna do?
Please don’t, P’Niran.
You jerk keep accusing people
with no evidence.
You’re hilarious, you know that?
Where were you an hour ago?
I was in a judo match.
There were like 10 witnesses.
Don’t be stupid.
I don’t believe you.
Go get some evidence.
You’re asking for evidence?
Now you’re asking for evidence?
Why didn’t you ask before
you pushed me and punched me earlier?
All you deserve
is a beating!
- Bring it. What the hell is wrong with you?
- No, P’Niran.
You don’t want to be put on probation.
This time, you could actually get suspended.
You shouldn’t have stopped me earlier.
Please calm down.
Damn, this is so frustrating.
On a scale of 1 to 10,
how mad were you at the time?
I don’t know.
Did you know?
I want you to try this.
When you’re angry, tell yourself
your amygdala is at an 8 out of 10
on the anger scale.
Scientifically speaking,
if we mention the part of our brain
that controls our emotions,
it helps us calm down.
Because that switch gets turned off
when we’re angry.
Who would be as calm as you?
I’m not calm.
Earlier, I was 9/10 mad
when he pushed you.
This method helped me.
Did you lose a Sports Day match today?
It wasn’t that serious.
I’ve been following Coach Ong’s
new schedule for me.
Why?
What did he call to tell you this time?
Don’t blame your coach or anyone else.
I saw it myself.
Huh?
You went to watch me at school?
Yes.
You didn’t tell me.
I didn’t want to distract you.
But when I saw you lose, I couldn’t stand it.
I don’t want to do it anymore.
Do you realize that
even your grades are dropping?
What have you been doing lately?
Huh?
Are you seriously not going to
get a single thing right?
You don’t even care about studying.
Can we not talk about this?
Tell me honestly.
Without judo, what would you be?
You keep asking stuff like this.
Have you ever asked me if I really liked it?
I mean, it makes no sense.
How do you go from being a national athlete
to an incompetent slacker like this?
What’s a competent person like, Dad?
Is it someone like you
who’s the reason
Mom has been gone from us all this time?
Niran.
I’ve always thought
I wanted Mom to come back to us.
But you keep destroying that belief.
You know why?
Because I don’t even freaking want
to live here myself!
Right here!
With you!
If you’re so tough, go get your mom back.
Mom loves me.
I could follow her.
She’d be waiting for me anyway.
Hi, Mom.
(Hello, Niran.)
(This weekend,)
(do you want to
grab something to eat with me?)
Of course.
I was literally just thinking of you.
I want to see you so much.
I’ve decided on something
and want to tell you about it.
(Oh, really?)
(Good.)
(We can talk about it.)
(See you soon.)
(I miss you, son.)
(Bye-bye.)
Are you nervous?
A little bit.
Oh.
Hey, Niran.
- Hi.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
How have you been?
So-so.
Nothing much.
What about you, Mom?
You invited me to eat out.
Is there something you want to tell me?
You usually visit me at home.
We don’t get to see each other very often,
so I wanted to bring you here
for some good food.
How’s school?
Have you thought about
what you want to study next?
Not yet.
Hey, Niran.
I heard you’re into sports, right?
Yes.
I’m mainly doing judo now.
Wow.
You’re amazing.
Let’s eat first.
We can talk more later.
Okay.
Let’s begin.
Here.
Eat up.
I ordered that for you.
Thank you.
Try this.
Aww, thank you.
You’re giving this to me first?
You’re not going to eat first?
Have some too, Niran.
I heard about your judo ranking, Niran.
Yeah.
Dad seems very disappointed in me.
Are you disappointed in me?
Not at all.
I’ve never been disappointed in you.
No matter what your judo ranking is,
I’ll always be proud of you.
I’m serious.
I mean it.
Thank you, Mom.
I’ll always be rooting for you too, Niran.
Don’t put too much pressure on yourself.
Next time you have a match, let me know.
I want to go cheer you on.
Mm.
And about your further studies,
there’s no need to pressure yourself.
If you can’t figure it out yet,
don’t force yourself.
You can go to university anytime, right?
Yes, Mom.
Once I figure it out, you’ll be the first to know.
I actually want you to
take me to apply to university.
Who knows? I might move in with you too.
If you have a spare room for me.
Anytime.
Niran, actually,
there’s something
I want you to be the first to know.
SON
Thank you.
Well, I’m…
I’m getting married to Uncle Rit.
But it’ll probably be a while
before the actual wedding.
This is what I wanted you to know
before anyone else.
Congratulations, Mom and Uncle Rit.
I'll definitely be there.
It’s your wedding, Mom.
I wouldn’t miss it.
I’ve never been to your wedding before.
(One thing’s for sure.)
(I can’t bring Mom back, just like Dad said.)
(But will I get to live with her?)
SON
(I’m still not sure.)
I just want my house to be
a place where you can do anything.
You can cry and be sad.
There’s no one to be embarrassed around.
I’m here.
What are you looking at?
Haven’t you ever seen a 12th-grader cry?
I’m here.
Why did you have to show up now?
This is so embarrassing.
Just pretend I’m not here.
How am I supposed to do that?
You’re staring at me.
You can wipe your tears with my shirt.
Are you going to take it off?
I’m wearing a vest underneath.
It’s fine.
No, don’t take it off.
If you do, I’ll be mad at you.
I’m going to buy some tissues.
I have some.
Then why did you act like
you were going to take your shirt off?
Oh.
Um, I thought that’d be cooler.
Come with me.
Come hang out at my house.
Why should I go there?
Well,
I just want my house to be
a place where you can do anything.
You can cry and be sad.
There’s no one to be embarrassed around.
I might be embarrassed around your brother.
You can stay in my room.
Fine. I’ll go.
Where are my tissues?
Oh.
They’re with P’Cheewin.
This is the first time Cheewa
has brought a friend home.
It’s totally not normal.
Even his best friend Jomyut
has never been there.
But Jomyut and Newton
came to your birthday party.
Cheewa!
I was trying to set you up.
Don’t sink the ship yet.
What ship?
A sailboat, I guess.
I taught you how to flirt the other day.
Haven’t you learned anything?
P’Cheewin!
Sorry. Slip of the tongue.
Do you want me to keep my distance
so you brothers can talk freely?
Just keep walking like this.
It’s okay.
Looks like it’s about to rain.
Let’s hurry.
Yeah, let’s go.
Hey, make yourself at home, Niran.
Okay. Thank you, P’Cheewin.
Mm.
Let’s go to my room.
Here. Let me put your stuff away.
Thank you.
Can I use the bathroom first?
Of course.
Okay.
That way.
Please wait here.
Wow.
Do you want to play a game?
There’s a game?
Yes.
Okay.
But if you lose,
you’d better not cry like a baby.
You’re the only one crying.
Watch it.
But if I cry because I have a soft spot for you,
please comfort me gently.
What are you even saying?
You little kid.
Cheewa, step it up.
I’m fighting.
Do you even know how to play a game?
Here.
Why are you smiling?
Focus on the game.
I am.
I can’t with the way you said, “I am.”
Hey, don’t pretend to lose!
I’m not.
I won't flick you anymore.
Your nose is all red.
Let me write on your face instead.
Can you see when we’re this close?
Not clearly.
How about this close?
It’s clear now.
So you mean if we’re any farther apart,
you can’t see clearly anymore?
Whether you can see clearly or not,
you’re getting your face painted.
Aha.
Let me ask you something.
According to science,
if I rub it a lot and the number shows up,
will I win the lottery if I buy that number?
No, you won’t. That’s just superstition.
Really?
Mm.
I think I’m enjoying this.
I’m sorry.
About what?
I let you cry for so long.
By the time I found you,
your eyes were all red.
You were there all alone.
I should’ve gone and sat next to you sooner.
Why are you apologizing?
It’s not your fault, Cheewa.
I want to be by your side at a time like this.
And I want you to know
I’m here for you.
Even though I’m not the hair on your head,
I’m the one in your heart.
Mm.
Thanks.
There’s a planet really far away from Earth.
It’s farther away than you can imagine.
It’s in a solid state.
But what’s really special is
it’s a solid that can absorb liquids really well.
Today, I’m going to be that planet
that helps absorb your tears.
Will you let me?
♪ Whenever you need me ♪
♪ Just know I’m keeping you in my sight ♪
The planet might be flooded, you know.
Let this planet be flooded.
We’ll float together.
♪ And I’ll still be here ♪
♪ Every turn, I’ll be near ♪
♪ Even on starless nights ♪
♪ I’ll be by your side ♪
♪ Right here for life ♪
♪ Just like you prayed to the stars ♪
♪ I’ll be by your side ♪
I’ll do it myself.
I’ll find evidence to prove I’m not the bad guy.
How will you proceed?
Most of the time, Oy gets bullied when he passes the science building.
So we have to lure them to the science building.
But what if the real culprit is a ghost?
We have to look for a ghost?
P’Niran, are you okay?
Are you worried about me?
Did you know?
If you keep beating around the bush,
you lose 20% of the time in your life.
Hey, don’t get smart with me.